# Ahmad Ali

### Full stack Developer - London, UK

Ahmad Ali Portfolio LinkedIn Profile Github Account

+(44) 7383 164 194 ahmad-ali14@zohomail.eu

### **SUMMARY**

Educated to degree level with 1 years' experience in web development. This has given me skills in JS: MERN, PHP: WP\_API, DB: MONGO, SQL, HTML and CSS. Currently seeking a position as a Web Developer that will utilise my skills and experience.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Freelancer, London— Freelance Web Developer

April 2019 - PRESENT

- Developed and designed websites for clients. 04/2019 to Present.
- Gained the experience of adjusting the products depending on the client's needs, and also the power of dealing with clients.
- Continued maintenance of my clients' websites, gained knowledge for after-sale practices.
- List of all projects with their links on the right >>

### **Other Work History**

September 2016 - March 2019

- Pharmacist community pharmacy full time 2 years.
- Science Translator Arabic / English I Believe In Science freelance volunteer - 1 year.
- Social Media Marketer Mind and World freelance 2 years.
- Medical Representative Malva Herbal Cosmetics part-time 6 months.

### **EDUCATIONS**

- **Kiron Open Higher Education,** Germany— computer science 2018 2020, Associate.
- **Damascus University**, Syria— pharmacy degree 2016
- **Further Education**, online 20 courses, list <u>here</u>

### **SKILLS**

- Javascript, React.js, Node.js
- databases: mongodb, sql
- Php: wordpress, wp api
- Html, css, bootstrap, jquery
- Rest api, git, npm

- Roye Interiors LTD interior design (php).
- Hex Luxury LTD online shop, home accessories (php, wp).
- Dg-url npm library works with urls (node.js).
- <u>Prfl20</u> elegent wordpress theme (php).
- E-Cart e-commerce app (MERN stack, stripe).
- Socialo social media app (serverless, MERN, redux)
- Coronavirus monitor
- Weather application
- ADPs API
- More Projects >>

PROJECTS